drnajeeblectures.com 2014-02-13

# Dr. Najeeb Lectures - Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

EFFECTIVE DATE: DECEMBER 7, 2013

Dr. Najeeb Lectures ("www.DrNajeebLectures.com") respects the privacy of people who use the www.DrNajeebLectures.com website or other www.DrNajeebLectures.com services. This privacy policy reflects the current information practices of www.DrNajeebLectures.com. Should there be any future changes to our privacy policy, we will continue to post them on this page.

In this policy, "you" or "your" refers to any person or entity subscribing to and/or using the Service ("Users"). Unless otherwise stated, "DrNajeebLectures," "we," or "our" will refer collectively to [www.DrNajeebLectures.com](http://www.drnajeeblectures.com/).

Dr. Najeeb Lectures has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements ](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html)including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal data. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, www.DrNajeebLectures.com. 

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy48783%20=%20'DrNajeebLectures'%20+%20'@';%20addy48783%20=%20addy48783%20+%20'gmail'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy48783%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy48783\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[DrNajeebLectures@gmail.com](mailto:DrNajeebLectures@gmail.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

**Collection of Data**

Anonymous Information: For each visitor to our web page, our web server automatically recognizes anonymous data that is not linked to your personal data, such as your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring website addresses.

Personal data: When you register as a member or request information, we will use our registration and online enrollment forms to collect personal data, such as your full name, e-mail address, telephone numberand educational background. In addition, if you contact us via an e-mail or offline, we may collect the personal data that you voluntarily provide us at that time. You can visit most of the public pages on our website site without giving us any personal data.

**Use of Data**

We will share your personal data with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.  We do not sell your personal data to third parties.The information we collect is used for the purpose for which you specifically provided the personal data,

·       to improve the content of our web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual user,

·       used to notify users about updates to our website,

·       shared with agents or contractors who assist in providing support for our internal operations,these agents are authorized to use your personal data only as necessary to provide support to us

·       used by us to contact users for marketing purposes, used by us to contact users for employment opportunities,

·       disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process,

·       to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website,

·       to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others,

·       to any other third party with your prior consent to do so,

·       to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting the website, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal data, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal data.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online or in regards to technical or billing or product related issues when deemed necessary during our regular office hours.

**Cookies**

We use cookies to store users' preferences, record session information, such as items that users add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert users to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when users return to our site, customize Web page content based on users' browser type, or other information that the user sends.

A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent by a website and stored on your visitor's computer. Cookies are small files and will not pose any significant disk space concerns. Some cookies used by the www.DrNajeebLectures.com site may remain on the user's computer after they leave the website, but most are set to expire within 30-365 days. You can disable our cookies using the cookie-menu on your web browser, but doing so will prevent you from taking advantage of customization and certain security features.

**3 rd Party Tracking**

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. 

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

Or our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. web beacons / web bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personal data.

**Flash LSO s**

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit.  Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored.  Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.  To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: 

[**http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118**](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118)

**Security**

The security of your personal data is important to us.  We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy59219%20=%20'DrNajeebLectures'%20+%20'@';%20addy59219%20=%20addy59219%20+%20'gmail'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy59219%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy59219\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[DrNajeebLectures@gmail.com](mailto:DrNajeebLectures@gmail.com).

**Transmission of Personal Data**

The user acknowledges and agrees that by providing www.DrNajeebLectures.com with any information through the site, the user automatically consents to the transmission of such personal or proprietary user information over international borders, as necessary, for processing in accordance with www.DrNajeebLectures.com standard business practices.

**Review and Correction  **

Upon request, we offer users the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, unique identifiers, transaction information, or delete their account. Users may send their requests to correct, update or delete their information by sending an e-mail or writing to us at the address below or by updating their profile by logging on through their account at [www.DrNajeebLectures.com](http://www.drnajeeblectures.com/).

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.  

**Links to 3 rd Party Sites**

Our web site includes links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Dr. Najeeb Lectures. If you submit personal data to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit.

**Testimonials**

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy81839%20=%20'DrNajeebLectures'%20+%20'@';%20addy81839%20=%20addy81839%20+%20'gmail'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy81839%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy81839\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[DrNajeebLectures@gmail.com](mailto:DrNajeebLectures@gmail.com).

**Maintaining Privacy**

As stated above, www.DrNajeebLectures.com will maintain the confidentiality of all user communications, which contains personal data transmitted directly to www.DrNajeebLectures.com. Postings by a user on any public arena, such as a message board or in any chat room, will not and cannot be protected as confidential. Any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, please contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Changes To This Policy**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this web site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or suggestions on how to improve our privacy to all users, please contact us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy82496%20=%20'DrNajeebLectures'%20+%20'@';%20addy82496%20=%20addy82496%20+%20'gmail'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy82496%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy82496\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[DrNajeebLectures@gmail.com](mailto:DrNajeebLectures@gmail.com).

Federico Geraldino # 17, Torre Dona Tema, 3A 

Santo Domingo 

Dominican Republic
